export const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Why should I rent a car with Get Your's?",
    answer:
      "Get Your's is one of the top rated car rental services in India. When you rent a car with us, you sign up for a clean, sanitized vehicle with a reliable and unmatched service quality. We offer intercity, local cars at super affordable fares. When you book a trip with Get Your's, we go above and beyond to make your road trip memorable.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "How can I rent a car?",
    answer:
      "You can rent a car either by booking online on Get Your's's website or by calling us on 90454 XXXXX.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What are the types of models that are available for rent?",
    answer:
      "At Get Your's, we have a range of car models for rent that suits all your needs when it comes to travelling - 4 seater sedans (Etios, Amaze, Dzire), AC hatchbacks (Indica, Ritz, Micra), 6-7 seater SUVs (Innova, Ertiga, Xylo) to 12 seater minivans. You can also opt for luxury cars for rent.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "Does Get Your's provide car rentals for local and outstation travels?",
    answer:
      "Yes, Get Your's provides premium and affordable car rentals for local and outstation travel in over 2000 cities and towns in India.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "Do I need to pay any extra amount apart from the one listed here on the website?",
    answer:
      "No, you need not pay any extra amount apart from the one listed on the website. At Get Your's, we have a strictly transparent billing policy - what you see is what you pay. Before you proceed with your booking, refer to the ‘inclusions’ sections.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Can I rent a car for a day, week or month?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you can rent a car with Get Your's for a day, week or month. To avail the best offers on long term rentals, contact our customer support on 90454 XXXXX.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What happens if I return the car late?",
    answer:
      "We understand that sometimes there can be last-minute changes in your plans, and we will try our best to accommodate them. But in situations where it can cause trouble to the next user (ie, the person whose booking starts after your ends), we cannot allow late returns. Please refer to our Fee policy for more details on late fees and extension charges",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What documents do I need to take the delivery of my car?",
    answer:
      "While taking the delivery of your car, you will need to show your ORIGINAL Driving License and ID proof (same as the ones whose details you provided while making the booking). These documents will be verified for validity. In case these documents are unavailable/invalid/unverifiable, your booking will be subject to cancellation. Get Your's decision in this matter will be final and binding. Please note that driving license printed on A4 sheet of paper (original or otherwise) will not be considered as a valid document.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "How do I check-out from my booking?",
    answer:
      "On your return, please check-out from your booking using our website. You also have the option of calling us to notify. Even if you forget to notify us, you will be charged only till the actual end time of your booking.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What if I leave something in Get Your's car?",
    answer:
      "Well, we will do our best to help you find your belongings if you inform us soon enough. But as you can imagine, we cannot guarantee it since finding it back is not fully in our control. So, please check the car thoroughly before handing it back to us.",
  },
];
